[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Mongo came into Rock Ridge in the movie Blazing Saddles, the Waco Kid said to Bart, No, no, dont do that. If you ........... him youll just make him mad. Fill in the missing word in the quote.", "correct_answer": "shoot", "incorrect_answers": ["abuse", "kiss", "arrest"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the first Superman movie Jor-El tells Clark not to get involved in what?", "correct_answer": "The affairs of humans", "incorrect_answers": ["Jobs", "Women", "Reporters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fast Times at Ridgemont High was added to the list of films preserved by the U. S. National Film Registry in 2005.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Now the time has come. I put two bullets in my gun. One for me and one for you. Oh darling, it wil be so beautiful.  Can you name the movie in which this line was spoken?", "correct_answer": "Misery", "incorrect_answers": ["The Devils Advocate", "Memento", "The Notebook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played  Marine biologist Matt Hooper in the movie Jaws?", "correct_answer": "Richard Dreyfuss", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Houston", "Lee Horsley", "Robert Shaw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gondorff staggers to the table declaring, \u201cSorry I\u2019m late, I was takin\u2019 a crap!\u201d and sits opposite Lonnegan. This is a scene from which movie?", "correct_answer": "The Sting", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hustler", "The Godfather", "The Conversation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In every hierarchy each employee tends to rise to the level of his or her incompetence. What name do we give to this phenomenon?", "correct_answer": "The Peter Principle", "incorrect_answers": ["The William Principle", "The Matthew Principle", "The Johnson Principle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who performs Nobody Does It Better, the theme song of the movie The Spy Who Loved Me?", "correct_answer": "Carly Simon", "incorrect_answers": ["Maxine Nightingale", "Karen Young", "Amanda Lear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Operation Petticoat the captains journal of Lt. Cmdr. Matt T. Sherman begins on what date?", "correct_answer": "December 10, 1941", "incorrect_answers": ["December 25, 1941", "December 31, 1941", "December 7, 1941"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Dorothy, the main character in the 1939 movie, The Wizard of Oz?", "correct_answer": "Gale", "incorrect_answers": ["It was never mentioned", "Grey", "Gulch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ages of many men are mentioned in The Bible. Who is the only woman whose age is mentioned in The Bible?", "correct_answer": "Sarah", "incorrect_answers": ["Vashti", "Ruth", "Bathsheba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Convective rain occurs in regions with what daytime whether?", "correct_answer": "Hot during the day", "incorrect_answers": ["Dry during the day", "Cold during the day", "Moist during the day"]}]